Here we go!
This time we have Risa Irie of JuiceJuice and
and Sakura Ishiyama from JuiceJuice.
This show is about the behind-the-scenes of the production of various artists
We're going to take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
Our recording, rehearsal, etc.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
Now then, let's start with a behind-the-scenes look at the two MCs.
I've been spending a lot of time at home lately, doing personal work.
If I stayed cooped up all the time, I'd become a bit of a useless person, so I try to get out and about as much as possible.
I try to get outside and walk about 10,000 steps a day.
I also like nature very much, so I go to various places to see nature.
Wow. How far would 10,000 steps be in terms of distance?
I think it was less than 5 kilometers.
How far is five kilometers?
I think 10,000 steps is a lot!
But I feel like I've done that much when I was playing with my friends.
Really? I like walking too.
But I've never paid attention to the number of steps I've taken.
Next time I go for a walk, I'll pay attention to the number of steps I take.
How many steps am I taking?
I'd like to see how many steps I take.
And me, Ishiyama...
I'm a member of Morning Musume・23's Rio Sakurai.
I went to her birthday event.
I went with my classmate Akari Endo.
I was there to cheer for the unmarried.
The day flew by so fast and I had so much fun.
The costumes were really cool. And the costumes are really cool.
It looks like it fits Rio.
It was really cool.
And the backstage is really fun.
There were some songs that were bought and changed.
I've never done a birthday event before, so I'm not sure if I'll be able to make it to the next one.
I've never been to a birthday event before, so I've never been to a birthday event before.
I've been to a lot of people's birthday events, but
I can't imagine what it's like.
I really don't know what it's like.
I don't know what it's really like, but I'll practice a lot so that I won't be nervous or anxious.
I'm going to practice a lot so that I won't be nervous or anxious.
Yes, I can really do everything I want to do at the birthday event.
What kind of costume I want to wear, what kind of song I want to sing, what kind of song I want to start, what kind of corner I want to do, etc.
I can decide what songs I want to sing, what kind of songs I want to start, what kind of corners I want to do, and so on.
You can make really great memories every year.
Please do your best!
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
Now, let's start off with this time's up-camera!
Watch the music video shooting of "Lonely Bus" from the latest single by Yoshikazu Miyamoto!
Music
Good morning. Today we are going to shoot the music video for "Lonely Bus,
The song has a rather sad sound, but it sings about various emotions, so I hope the music video will show those emotions, and I think it will be gorgeous to drive the bus.
I am looking forward to seeing the finished product and will do my best.
The first time, we will shoot while the car is actually driving.
ran
purser
ran purser
me me
povår
tee
ki
tage
Thank you for watching!
Goodbye hug
The right profile reflected in the window
I feel like I'm laughing and I feel like I'm crying
You don't know, no one knows
Me, me, me
Let's go to meet
The weakness that believed there must be a limit
I want to have the strength to stop it with my hand
I'll live my life away from you that's all
It's okay, I believe all
Until we reach the unexplored future, the years of popular sasakaku
Morning glow illuminates my eyelids and tells me that today is the day
My eyes are reflected in this world, which seems simple but is complex
I'm beyond the darkness and the pain, just like me
I'm a good fit for you, aren't I?
I thought there was supposed to be an eternity, didn't I?
I thought love would never change, didn't I?
We'll live apart, and yet
We'll believe all
One.
Two.
Three.3
Eight. Nine.
10 Yes! Yes, cut!
Yes, we have just finished shooting the music video for Lonely Bus!
This time, I was very nervous because it was a very new feeling, especially when it comes to dancing.
I was very nervous.
But I think I did the best I could do.
I hope you will pay attention to my dance and facial expressions.
I saw your Lonely Bus.
You can see even through the screen how small her face is!
She was so beautiful, and the bus was just as beautiful as Miyamoto-san.
The scenery was beautiful, and the bus was filmed from morning till night.
I thought it was amazing that you were able to bring out Ms. Miyamoto's colors on the bus.
As the title says, there were a lot of buses in the film.
I've never filmed on a bus before, so I thought it was very fresh.
I really love Miyamoto-san who sings very quiet songs, so I want to see a lot of this music.
I love her singing very quiet songs, so I hope to see many more of her songs.
That's all for the making of the shooting of the music video for "Lonely Bus" by Yoshikazu Miyamoto.
I want to get the strength to accept the weakness that I believed I should have
I want to get the strength to accept it
That's all there is to living apart
It's going to be okay
Don't worry, it's going to be okay
Next, here it is!
Morning Musume。23すごいフィーバー Vocal RecordingMorning Musume。23 Sukkoku Fever Vocal Recording
From Morning Musume。23's latest single
Please take a look at the vocal recording of Rio Kitagawa, the amazing Fever!
Amazing, amazing!
Thank you for watching!
Wow, wow, wow!
Amazing, amazing, amazing.
With just one person's will, it will come back to life.
One person's will can change the times.
Rinokishi...
The only one who will...
One person's will will change the times.
Yes
One person's will will change the times
It's all over
One lie is the end
One lie, one lie, and it's all over.
In the A melody, there's this "amazing, amazing, amazing" part.
But if this S is too long, the rhythm slows down.
You have to say, "Wow!" like this.
I can do it when I say it with my mouth like this.
But you can't keep saying "ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta" while the music is saying it.
If I didn't say it, it would be out of place.
It's more than just shrugging it off together.
Yes, I'm here!
Kiki, I'm here, Rukya!
Yes, sir.
ED.
Seishun zenkokuteiru kotoI'm putting all my youth on the line for you.
You should know that.
I spend more time with you than I do with my family.
It's been a long time.
I'm ticking.
I'm marking time.
Yes, sir.
It's what I do in my youth.
I spend more time with my family than I do with my own.
I've been here longer than I've been with my family.
Do you know that?
Do you know?
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, sir.
Do you know?
I know in my head that I'm supposed to say "youth" because there are four letters in the word "youth" even though there are only two letters in the word "youth," but when I actually sing it, I feel like putting the letters in.
But when I actually sing it, I feel like putting letters in between the words.
So I was really focusing on the pause without words in the debut melody.
That part was really difficult.
Thank you for watching!
Whenever!
whenever!
Above all...
Yes, sir.
Aya...
Yes
Burna burnt or scorched fire
feeling of a throat burned
yes
Yes
Enjoy it to the fullest
Above all, shine!
Tee-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta-ta...
This vowel is really very important.
One more sound but two words
One sound, two words, one sound, two words.
It goes on for eight times.
You have to keep the rhythm very well.
I have to keep that in mind.
I'm sure I'll make everyone happy
was also very difficult.
Because it's a cue, it tends to get buried.
When I did the "lulu lulu"...
That's why I had to push the "u" part of the other "wu" part like this.
I had to rework the "u" part like this.
The rhythm and the expression and the pause.
It was very difficult to find the perfect balance between the rhythm and the expression.
Ruuuuuuuuuuu!
Ha!
Hey, I'll make you happy!
Fever night is here!
Goo, you're a cow
You're gonna make everybody happy
Fever night
I love Rio Kitagawa's voice so much.
I love Rio Kitagawa's voice so much, and every time I see her recordings on Apkami, I watch them all the time. Whenever Kitagawa-san's recordings come out on Apkami, I watch them for a long time.
Morning's unique rhythm is amazing.
I would never have been able to do it myself.
I also felt that the pitch of the music must be very difficult.
It was a lot of fun to watch.
Yes, I thought that this song seems to be very difficult to glide through.
I don't know how to say it, but it seems to be very difficult to memorize the rhythm and the notes by listening to the tentative song.
I thought it would be very difficult to memorize the rhythm and the notes after hearing the tentative song.
And then, at this stage of recording, Kitagawa-san sang it as if it was almost completed.
I was really impressed.
That's all for Morning Musume。 23 Vocal Recording of Rio Kitagawa's "VERY FEVER"!
Thank you for all your hard work!
Thank you for watching!
Can you hear me? I can hear you.
When you're ready, I'll ask you to warm up your throat and make some adjustments, and then I'll give you one.
Yes, please.
Okay, let's try one. Yes, please.
Music
People say.
I wonder if that part was just supposed to be normal.
The rhythm of the latter eight times of praying may you be happy
May you be happy and pray
Lou's position is a little awkward.
Lou's position is a little bit twitchy.
Let's be a little careful there.
From 30,000 years ago to me living here and now
Love that flows like a miracle
A love deeper than the sea
Wrapped in feelings deeper than the sea Wrapped up and unknowingly kept alive
Thank you for being born
Thank you, thank you for the bond
I've always loved the song "Kizuna" by Asuke Matsuura.
I've loved it since I was a teenager.
I've always wanted to sing it somewhere.
But I haven't had much of a chance to sing it.
I've always wanted to sing it, and I've been keeping it warm.
And now I'm 23 years old.
I've been thinking about all the things I've been through recently.
The lyrics are very beautiful.
I think there are a lot of people who don't know about it.
I think there are a lot of people who don't know the lyrics.
That's why I want them to know about it.
I chose this song because I want people to know about it, and also because I want them to live their lives to the fullest.
When I was a teenager, I used to sing at home, just going along with the music.
I felt like I was just singing because I wanted to sing.
But there were lyrics that I could really relate to.
But there are parts of the lyrics that I can relate to
There are parts of me that I still don't understand.
I thought the lyrics were wonderful when I sang them.
But you recorded the song and also shot the video, right?
I always try to keep my face from looking like a madman.
I'm always a little worried about it, so I'm a little anxious about it.
Yes, that's why my posture is always messed up.
I also try not to move my hands too much.
But I do sweat a little more.
I don't usually shoot a whole song, so it was nice to work up a good sweat today.
It's great to be able to work up a good sweat today.
Shall we go then? Shall we go then?
I can't say what I really feel.
She's a serious girl, but she's good at it.
Maybe she's good at it.
A magazine from only 10 years ago.
And the fashions are funny.
You can't beat the devil with fashion.
I can do it now.
100 times
Safe
Earth is discothèque, fight otometic
Not a single experience is a waste of time
Life is so dramatic, play on, Milesic
You never know what you're gonna get unless you try, 'cause there are consequences in life.
Say hello
Say hello was my first original song as a trainee
It was the first original song I recorded as a trainee, and I may have participated in the recording of other songs as well, but it was the first time I received a solo part for an original song.
So Say Hello was the first time I was given a solo part in a CD.
I chose this song because I had a lot of memories of this song, including the praise I received from my seniors when I sang it at a Halo Project concert.
When I used to sing this song as a trainee, we basically sang almost in unison, so I didn't really put my feelings into it, but I didn't have time to do so.
I didn't have time to put my true feelings into it.
I sang by following the rules that were set by everyone, like "I can't say it out loud".
But when I sing all by myself, I can sing so freely, and it's so much fun, and it's a different kind of fun.
I didn't think I would become someone who liked this kind of funk groove so much 10 years ago.
So at that time
I was just happy to get a solo part, but this song is a bit like my current taste in music.
I think it's a great song and it's the first time I got a solo part.
There are so many great songs in Hello Project, and I'm going to graduate from Hello Project from now on.
Hello Project is full of great songs, and I'm graduating from Hello Project.
I was singing with the feeling that I wanted people to realize that, so I hope that my message will be conveyed to as many people as possible.I was singing with the feeling of wanting people to notice me, so I hope that many people will be able to understand that.
Yes, I've seen Yume Kishimoto's singing videos.
I often get so much energy from your songs.
When I want to motivate myself to sing before recording
I would search for your recordings on UpCam and listen to them.
and listen to them.
I was so happy to be able to enjoy her solo videos again.
I was very happy to be able to enjoy your solo videos again.
Your graduation concert was really nice and cool.
I'm sure we'll be able to hear more of your songs in the future.
I'm sure we'll be hearing more songs from you in the future.
I'm sure we'll be able to hear more of her singing in the future, so I'm really looking forward to it.
Yes, I am Silman.
When I was a trainee, I performed a song called "Say Hello".
I was told that they were going to audition for this song, so I was given the song for Say Hello.
As I watched the video, I remembered something like that.
I was also able to see your graduation concert live at the Nippon Budokan.
The black pants style graduation outfit was very Kishimoto-san-like.
It was so cool to see your core strength and coolness
I thought it was really cool that Kishimoto-san's core strength and coolness came out so clearly.
That's all for the making of Yume Kishimoto's singing video.
Morning Musume・23 featuring Mizuki Fukumura
Never Ending Shine
Now on tour
You're working hard, you're so cool!
Thank you for watching!
It's time to say goodbye to Fukami, brought to you by Irisa and Sakura Ishiyama!
We've seen a lot of videos this time, but I, Ishiyama...
I, Ishiyama, was impressed by the recording of Rio Kitagawa. I, Ishiyama, was very impressed by the video of Rio Kitagawa's recording.
I forgot to mention earlier that when she sings while keeping the rhythm in the back, I really like the way she stops singing.
I forgot to mention that I really like the way she stops singing when she sings while keeping the rhythm in the back of the song.
I'd like to see that kind of thing again when the video is released.
Yes, I was very impressed with Yume Kishimoto's singing video.
I was really impressed by Yume Kishimoto's singing video, and I think it's really amazing that she can cheer people up with her singing.
I would like to do my best to be a person who can give power to people by singing more and more like you.
I would like to continue to do my best so that I can be a person who can give power to people with my songs like you.
In this issue of APKAMI, we will go behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the UPFRONT GROUP.
Please subscribe to our channel so that we can introduce you to what you don't normally see!
This time, I'll be talking with Risa Irie of JuiceJuice and
and Sakura Ishiyama of JuiceJuice.
Good bye.
Next time on Apkami, we have Subiki Factory, Freedom Dance Lesson if you only have fantasies!
And we will be showing a makeup lesson of Anna members from Ochanoma!
Enjoy!